Making Love is a drama, music film directed by Ricky Tognazzi.
Costanza is drinking a beer in a Prague pub, a summer night in 1968, while a
violinist enters and starts playing a "canone inverso" for her.
It is not a case, that music and that violin have a
story behind that could concern her.
It is the love story between Jeno Varga and the music, between Jeno and Sophie.
Jeno Varga, played by Hans Matheson.
Sophie Levi, played by Mélanie Thierry.
David Blau, played by Lee Williams.
Violinista / Jeno Varga Adulto, played by Gabriel Byrne.
Baron Blau, played by Ricky Tognazzi.
Barone Blau, played by Peter Vaughan.
Punch-Drunk Love is a 2002 American absurdist romantic comedy drama film,
produced, written and directed by Paul Thomas Anderson.
Adam Sandler stars as an entrepreneur with social anxiety who falls in
love with his sister's co-worker, played by Emily Watson.
The supporting cast includes Philip Seymour Hoffman and Luis Guzmán.
After working on his third film Magnolia, Anderson planned to make his next film around 90
minutes, with Sandler in mind as the lead due to Anderson's love for him and his films.
It features the video art of Jeremy Blake in the form of visual interludes.
Punch-Drunk Love was produced by Columbia Pictures, Revolution Studios, New Line Cinema
and Ghoulardi Film Company, and distributed by Sony Pictures Releasing.
It premiered at the 2002 Cannes Film Festival on May 19, 2002 before being
released theatrically in the United States on November 1, 2002.
The film received positive reviews from critics, with
Sandler's performance receiving widespread acclaim.
However, the film was a box-office disappointment, grossing $24.7
million against its $25 million production budget.
A favorite of several prominent filmmakers, it has been included in
lists of the greatest movies of the 21st century.
It was also a launchpad for Sandler to pursue dramatic or
unconventional film roles outside of his usual mainstream comedies.
The film explores themes of friendship, based on novel or book,
violin, world war ii, prague, czech republic.
The tone is emotional.